No living creature was hurt
during the production of this show.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Soldiers!
God protect us all.
Coming from that direction!
Run! Run!
Two Days Ago
Hi all.
Malhun Hatun.
Where are these rugs going to?
We will take them
to Harmankaya, Ayse Hatun.
Why are you going to the infidels?
Let them pick up the rugs by themselves.
This is Osman Bey's order.
This is not an aimless action, Ayse Hatun.
We have a plan.
We are ready to set off.
Keep your eyes open, look sharp.
We are not going for a delivery.
We are going to learn what's going on
in Harmankaya.
Eyvallah. (Okay)
It's time to conquest, Aygül.
- Let's conquer the infidel from inside.
- Let's do it.
You are entrusted to Allah.
Go at once, come back at once
Inshallah.
May your way be open, Inshallah.
Eyvallah (thank you).
Off we go.
Bilecik Castle.
Kayı's trading is about to stop...
...while our caravans are all over
Bithynia.
We gain power as Osman loses.
To the unity of
the noble Lords of Bithynia.
To us being able to have the Priest back.
To Osman's defeat.
Tell me about the problem,
Akca Dervish.
It seems significant.
My Bey, we have been trying to complete
the orders from Iznik for a long time...
...but the orders remained unsold.
Osman Bey, we wouldn't have spent
all our savings to complete the orders...
if we hadn't trusted you.
We made a great loss, Osman Bey.
What are we going to do now, Osman Bey?
Some of you are older than me.
We haven't let anyone down since
my ancestor Ertugrul Ghazi.
Don't worry.
Your loss will be covered.
- We don't let anyone down.
- May Allah bless you.
We knew you wouldn't
let us down, Osman Bey.
May Allah Bless you too.
Thank you all.
They left my tradesmen in the lurch!
I'll make them pay for it.
You are known as the voice
of the oppressed, Osman Bey.
You don't let your people down.
You make the cruels pay for what they do.
You are going to get through this.
I will, my Sheik, I will.
Can I come in, my Sheik?
Come my Boran Alp.
My Bey, there's news from Rogatus.
He invites you to his castle along with
the neighboring Lords.
As you see, my Sheik.
As you see, brother.
They want to reap what they sow.
They want to discourage us.
My Bey, our situation is apparent.
The thing to do is clear...
...right, Osman Bey?
The peace is good, Osman Bey.
The thing to do is clear, brother.
We'll accept the invitation.
But...
A guest mustn't be empty-handed.
We'll bring them a present.
We are going to make them pay.
We are going to take revenge
for the oppressed.
- Boran!
- My Bey.
Let them know I accept their invitation.
As you order, my Bey.
My Sheik.
Bilecik Castle.
It was a great move, Rogatus.
I appreciate you.
I can't wait to see
the desperate face of Osman.
To be honest, the idea of seeing that
overweening Osman kneeling in front of us...
excites me more than the idea of
having the Priest back.
Osman will come here soon,
ready to surrender.
We are all excited to see that.
What are you doing, brother?
I am scaling.
I am previewing their
headless body, brother.
Kayı's Bey Osman Bey is here.
I appreciate that you accepted
my invitation, Osman Bey.
You sent an invitation, and we are here.
It's tradition,
we didn't come empty-handed.
Feodor!
Damn it!
What have you done, Osman Bey?
You are not going to die before
experiencing the pain that I am...
experiencing right now, Osman Bey.
I wanted you to notice the truth.
The truth is on the table which you wished
that I'd kneel in front of.
If one disobeys Osman Bey,
he shall die!
Listen to me now.
You wanted to ruin me and many Turkmens.
Do you think you can ruin Turks by
taking their gold away?
Tit-for-tat.
Your goods are mine.
No one has peace if Turk has no peace.
That's all I have to say.
We're leaving.
Osman.
He always finds a way out.
Feodor.
My loyal soldier.
We are really sorry for Feodor, Rogatus.
But there's even a more important
situation in front of us right now.
- What can be more important, Kosses?
- Guess what!
That Caravan, which carries
all of our goods...
...has already departed from Damascus.
Rogatus, don't let your anger
take over your brain.
Osman...
If Osman takes that too...
He'll knock us down!
I won't let this happen.
I am going to protect the caravan.
As we talked, Osman will come
around Castellion...
and I, among us, know him the best.
It's natural to know someone better when
he defeats you over and over again, I guess.
You watched me losing
like watching a tragedy.
Moreover, you left me alone
in front of Osman.
Do you hold me responsible for all
of this now?
I am sure you'll manage...
Nicola.
I, Aya Nicola...
will not let Osman touch that caravan.
I swear.
I won't let him.
Harmankaya Castle.
Inform Mari.
We brought the rugs she wanted.
Keep your eyes open Aygül.
Let's do this.
Malhun Hatun, what a surprise, welcome.
Thank you Mari.
I wanted to bring the rugs.
You did fairly well.
Meet Aygül.
She is Osman Bey's cousin.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Let's get in.
Sogut.
From now on, the trophy...
will be shared among the tradesmen
according to their loss...
due to the broken agreements with Lords.
Thank you, my Bey.
We knew you wouldn't let us down,
Osman Bey.
May Allah
Don't worry. We'll find new trade routes
and make new treaties if needed.
Be at ease.
-Thank you, Osman Bey.
-May Allah bless you, Osman Bey.
May Allah bless you too.
Osman Bey.
We've taken care of the problems
of the traders for now, thank Allah.
But I must say it, until we find new
routes, the people will die.
Who can we make treaties with, Osman Bey?
Even if the heathens block one way,
we have a thousand other, brother.
We'll find it.
Harmankaya Castle
Your sherbet is delicious.
You brought it to Harmankaya.
Thank you.
Enjoy it, Mari.
That day, we couldn't show you
the carpets.
For this reason, I wanted to bring
the completed ones.
You are kind.
It's actually good that not all of them
came at once. The lords don't know it.
I know, of course.
So, how will you take the rest?
Will the lords allow this?
There isn't a caravan coming soon.
If there was, we would hide them there.
The best is to wait.
That big caravan from Damascus, carrying
all the goods of the lords.
Isn't it coming soon?
Let us bring them with that caravan, then.
Unfortunately, Cornelia is mistaken.
That caravan isn't passing through
Turkish lands.
So, that won't do.
Then, we'll wait for your word, Mari.
We'll bring the rest when you want.
If you allow us.
Both our trade and friendship
please me. Stay in health.
Likewise, Malhun Hatun.
-You are always welcome here.
-Thank you.
May Allah bless your hands,
my wife.
Enjoy it.
Cerkutay.
Why aren't you eating, brother?
Didn't you like it?
No. When does Cerkutay ever not
like a meal?
It looks delicious.
So?
But my throat is locked.
Even water can't pass.
What's your trouble, brother?
It's like you've eaten lots of bulghur.
Tell us.
My trouble is great.
And its cure is so pretty.
I can't speak any words in front of
Aygül Hatun.
I want to marry her.
Tell me, how did you do this
marriage thing?
Show me a way.
Mine was so good.
Boran is right. He was also like you
until he finally spoke of marriage.
Brother, look. You will face her.
You will say it in one breath.
Without beating around the bush.
In one breath?
Yes.
You are Cerkutay.
Be brave.
Face her and say it in one breath.
I will say it in one breath!
But the girl is crazy.
Brother, inshallah she won't cut you.
Even if she does, you'll say that
I died for love.
Lovers don't die.
Neither does Cerkutay.
In one breath, right?
In one breath, brother.
In one breath?
It's delicious!
Enjoy it.
It's so good.
So good.
Look at you!
Mashallah to my Orhan!
He grows so fast.
Yes. He already grew
bigger than his clothes.
Mashallah to my lion!
We've overcome this as well, Bala Hatun.
Thank Allah.
This won't solve our problems but
it will ease them.
It'll help the tribe.
This was good. We relieved Osman Bey's
burdens, even if for a bit.
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Welcome, my bey.
Mashallah to my Orhan!
Mashallah to my Orhan.
Mashallah.
My bey, we delivered the carpets,
thank Allah.
Thank you.
Let's see.
Thank you, Malhun.
So, Malhun.
Tell me, what's the situation in
Harmankaya?
Did you notice anything?
How are the lords?
Mari was pleased to see the carpets.
She said that she can draw the curtain
without letting them notice anything.
A great caravan is coming.
It's an important caravan, my bey.
It's coming from Damascus.
All lords have good in it.
I knew that you wouldn't return
empty-handed, Malhun.
Thank you.
Now I will teach them a lesson.
They'll see what does it mean to touch
a wolf's food.
What's in your mind, Osman Bey?
To do what's in my mind,
we need to use the priest.
We put so much effort to take him.
Now it's time to use him.
How is the priest, my bey?
Are his wounds healed?
Kumral Abdal said that he is alright.
Nikola.
We have common enemies.
So are our causes.
And so should our ranks.
Speak more clearly, Rogatus.
Please.
These Palailogous'.
They think nothing but themselves.
There is nothing they can give you.
I don't want you to be sure, Rogatus.
After all, alliances aren't only
built...
by wars.
What's your offer, Rogatus?
The thing that returned Priest Gregor
to Osman.
This precious relic that Osman will
never give.
A relic?
What relic?
We can only find out when we have it.
We can only have it if we are together.
I'll think about your offer, Rogatus.
But there is something much more important
than this right now.
It's the caravan that's important for
all our futures.
I'm sure that you will protect
that caravan.
Aya Nikola isn't alone now.
Harmankaya Castle
He isn't dead, huh?
Is that so?
So...
where was he shot at that...
he could survive, Bahadır?
On his chest.
On his chest...
-On his shoulder!
-Oh, on his shoulder!
On here?
You don't even know where!
Fortunately, your incapability
resulted well.
It's good that the priest is alive.
This is your reward.
What's in your mind, Lord Kosses.
There is a reason that priest
returned to Osman.
Something he brought
from Constantinople.
It's precious.
You will find out what that is, Bahadır.
Consider it done.
I hope so...
Bahadır.
I hope so.
Don't bother, Priest Efendi.
I wanted to check your health.
I'm grateful for your concern.
But why am I here?
Where is Osman Bey?
You will be our guest in our lodge
for a while.
With the name of Allah.
This...
It's vinegared water.
With the name of Allah.
And this is honeyed water.
Both are healing.
When you take them together,
they are even better.
Not yet, Priest Efendi.
There is time.
This was the most delicious honey
I've ever tasted.
What makes the honey so delicious is
the vinegar you drank before it.
Look at Osman Bey's hawks.
Cerkutay.
It's not important but very
important at the same time.
Forget about it now. When will we
take the other heads?
You are impatient, right?
The time will come, brother.
We'll take their heads and
their castles.
We'll take them all.
We'll make it our home.
Inshallah.
Brothers, this is conquest.
Its time will come.
Until that time, you will
be patient, brother.
You tell them.
These weapons wouldn't stay tamed
with Bamsı Bey either.
They turn blunt if you don't wet
them with blood.
Then, Osman Bey should run us
for one battle after another.
So, Boran. You said conquest
and battle.
Sing us a song.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Yes.
Baykurt, come on.
With the name of Allah.
When you turned twenty...
He saw a sacred dream.
Against all the tyrants...
he is a hidden menace, Osman Bey!
He is a student of Edebali...
may the heathens be cursed...
he is the pride of Ertuğrul Ghazi...
Osman Bey is a different valiant!
He subdued many nations.
The sky cried on red banners.
He swung his claws on the tyrants.
Like a black wolf, Osman Bey!
On strong horses with
grey manes...
with tough armors and
sharp weapons...
with brave alps...
He wrote an epic, Osman Bey!
When the oppressed were crying...
the ground has shaken from
the call...
and a man emerged from its heart...
like a majestic tent, Osman Bey!
He subdued many nations.
The sky cried on red banners.
He swung his claws on tyrants.
Like a black wolf, Osman Bey!
Mashallah, brother.
Thank you, brother Boran.
Cerkutay, don't eat it.
Allahu Akbar.
May the peace, mercy, and blessings
of Allah be with you.
My Allah!
For your most precious name.
For the holiness of Celali.
For the greatest name.
For your prophets.
For their parents.
For the blood of the martyrs.
Accept my gratitude.
I don't have anything worthy
of your justice.
You treat me with your mercy.
Oh my Allah, mightiest of
the mighties.
You are capable of everything.
You destined us to pass the traps
of the heathens...
through your wisdom.
I opened my arms to worship you.
Accept it, my Allah.
Oh, the owner of everything!
My jihad is for you.
The sword I swing is for you.
It's to have your name rule
over the world.
To reach this holy dream...
give me and my lineage strength.
To beat the heathens,
give us strength.
Bless us to ruin their traps...
...that they set for us, Lord.
Triumph is yours.
Make us victorious!
Amin.
Salam Aleikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Inform Osman Bey.
We brought a present.
We will hand it in.
It's important.
I want to deliver myself.
Do not keep me waiting.
Turgut Bey!
I heard you let your alps hunt Catalans.
But things didn't go well.
I had a problem with the Catalans.
So, I did it right.
Mashallah (praise be).
You showed how valiant you are.
They lost their lives.
We had a common enemy.
That's right.
And every valiant needs a friend like you.
Thank you.
Not only them.
I will have much more to do for you after
what you have done for my tent, Osman Bey.
Everything has its time.
Eyvallah(see you) then.
Wait, Turgut Bey.
Wait there.
Goktug.
Bring the share of Turgut Bey
from the trophy.
As you order, my Bey.
Horses!
While you were fighting the enemy,
we finished them on the table.
We reserved your share, Turgut Bey.
Thank you.
He is trying to suppress us.
We should have been the ones who
brought the bodies of Catalans, brother.
Goktug, let it be, brother.
The betrayers are dead now.
Focus on the result.
Why would we be upset?
Right, right brother.
Harmankaya Castle.
We hosted Malhun Hatun very well.
She left satisfied.
However, you have to hear what you
are saying. Remember they are our enemy.
You are right, mistress.
Brother?
Why was Osman's Hatun here, Mari?
How dare you do business without
my information?
- Only for trade.
- What trade are you talking about, Mari?
We made an agreement with the Lords to defeat
Osman! What trade are you talking about?
I strongly remind you that I have
the same blood as you!
I am making my own plan!
How dare you make a plan
while I am alive!
Where are you going?
I am not done!
I am done!
I am going hunting! I don't think I will
come back until I calm down!
God knows the best.
Hello there.
Thank you.
Do you know where Aygül Hatun is?
What are you talking about?
Crazy! I am here.
No.
I am talking about the Aygül Hatun who
rises her sword...
shoots arrows, knocks out seven men
all alone.
Who were you talking about?
That dagger won't harm me.
Your looks that are sharper than a dagger
have already killed me, you tough girl.
Do you know what that is?
What is that?
This is a flower.
Are you serious?
When someone gives this to you...
something happens.
What is that?
Something.
What is that, Cerkutay?
Cerkutay, why are you keeping me
if you can't tell what it is!
Get out of my way!
Something happens.
Yes.
It's hard to talk when you are
a lover with a burning heart.
Sogut.
Our beautifully named glorious
prophet...
Hadrat Muhammed Mustafa...
"Peace be upon him."
Hadrat Isa (Jesus) was before Him.
He was one of the doors
opening to Jannah(heaven).
But Yahuda, one of his closest followers,
betrayed Jesus...
Yahuda's betrayal against Jesus was
for a bit of wealth.
He was a slave of his desires to
sell Jannah (heaven) for a handful of gold.
But, Cenab-i Haqq (Allah)...
made Yahuda hoisted by his
own petard.
What does Nisa Surah say?
With Allah's power,
A stranger was shown as Jesus to them...
They thought he was Jesus, and stretched
him on the crucifix.
Allah raised Jesus to His place
before...
they stretched Jesus on the crucifix.
So, they neither killed Jesus,
nor killed him.
However, the one they killed was shown
to them as Jesus.
You are right that Yahuda betrayed
holy Jesus.
But you are in a great delusion to think
that someone else was sacrificed.
- I saw a herd of pigs.
- Did you hunt them?
Be quiet!
Idiots!
Stay here.
That direction!
Come with me.
Let's go.
I am not in a delusion because those
are not my words.
If you want to argue, I won't refuse you,
Priest Efendi.
My Sheik, excuse me.
I want to talk to Priest Gregor
on an important subject.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(in the name of God, the merciful and compassionate.)
Tell me, Bahadir Alp.
You must have seen more Alps
compared to a Dervish.
Are you a loyal Alp to your Osman Bey...
like Pahlivan Dervish being loyal
to his Dervish?
Pahlivan Dervish is just as loyal as
any Kayi Alp.
Sheik Efendi.
Eyvallah (okay).
You recovered fast, Priest.
You look good.
Thank you. Yes, I'm fine.
Priest.
I know very well what this
mysterious relic is.
Since this shroud is more precious
than your life...
then it is our duty to preserve
it properly.
Do not worry.
First of all, I want you to know that.
I want to talk to you about another issue.
I want you to go somewhere.
Can you talk to me clearly, Osman Bey?
A village that is near to Kestel.
It is in the borders of İnegöl
feudal lands.
Everyone in the village is
Orthodox Christian.
But their situation is worse than ever.
They take all their assets under
the name of tax.
They even torture those who
want to oppose it.
I want you to salve these
oppressed co-religionists of yours.
How can I be helpful to them?
I couldn't even protect myself, Osman
Bey.
Haven't I told you just before, Priest?
Your life and your holy relic
are under our protection.
Do you think I will send you there alone?
Do not worry.
My soldiers will be with you too.
They will protect you, do not worry.
I want your existence and your words
to be a savior for the oppressed in there.
What do you want me to tell them?
The truth.
The truth, Priest.
I want you to tell them what you've been
through since you came to Söğüt.
I want them to know that the
truth will always defeat oppression.
I believe in your sincerity, Osman Bey.
I will go to that village.
Let's start preparations as soon
as possible.
Turgut Bey.
The poison needs to be removed.
Hold on.
Be a little patient.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
But whenever I see a snake,
I see you.
You have no idea that you are in the
den of the snakes.
Easy, easy.
Cornelia!
Come here.
You owe me another life, Miss Byzantium.
I don't like to be in debt to anyone. We
will be even.
Are you okay, Miss?
I'm okay.
Don't do anything.
Soldiers! Bring the horses here.
What did he tell you?
Osman knows that the holy relic is the
cross on which Jesus Christ was crucified.
A piece of the cross on which
Jesus was crucified.
He will never give it to us.
We will go to a village near Kastelion
by the will and protection of Osman.
The villagers are all Orthodox Christians.
Are we going to act on Osman's word?
You have just recovered.
She is here.
I hope nothing's wrong.
Aygül Hatun.
Cerkutay.
Say what you need to.
Do you remember the flower...
I gave you yesterday?
Its name is the flower of the mystery.
Whoever gives that flower to someone...
has to reveal his secret to that person.
I will tell you my secret.
I'm in love with you.
This secret is too much for both of us,
Cerkutay.
You revealed your secret, Cerkutay.
Brave Cerkutay.
Did you think loving someone is easy?
It's easy to endure its pleasure...
but when you endure the suffering of it,
it becomes love.
This is love, Cerkutay!
It enslaves even the sultans and
burns the lovers to ashes.
Don't give up on love.
You have to endure both the curse and
the bless.
Don't turn your back on love.
Love can't be turned away.
Burn, Cerkutay. Burn.
Inegol Frontier Village
Nearby Kastellion
It's him. The Priest!
He is coming!
Welcome, Priest.
Welcome.
Jesus Christ bliss you...
and forgive your sins.
I had many other things on my mind when
I was coming from Constantinople...
or rather, when I was escaping from
the Emperor's tyranny.
But as some of you have heard, God
crossed my path with Osman Bey.
Why did you stay in a Turk plain
instead of a feudal land, Priest?
Why didn't you go to the Lord Nicolo?
He would protect you.
He gives great value to the nobility.
May Jesus Christ's love be with you.
You are a very kind-hearted person.
But Nicolo wouldn't have done that.
For the power he wanted to gain, he would
leave me alone with the Emperor's tyranny.
You didn't go to the Lord Kosses too
because he is close to the Emperor.
We understand this. But why didn't you go
to the Lord Rogatus?
We heard that he is close to you.
He would protect you.
That's true.
I thought so too.
But Rogatus acted like the others
when it came to gaining power.
He left me stranded.
But Osman Bey kept me safe.
Moreover, when I saw the Christian
people and the church...
in Söğüt, I realized that this attitude
was not special to me.
I have never seen such justice
and mercy in any feudal land...
even though we are co-religionists.
I heard about the church in the village.
Each of them persecutes their
people for their personal gain.
They ignore people's most basic needs.
I heard about the church in this village.
Doesn't this state of the church
break your heart?
They do not meet the needs of
our church at all.
It is like a barn.
Osman Bey keeps the church in Söğüt
well-kept as if it were his own temple.
He governs the Christians fairly without
discriminating them from the Muslims.
I have a relative who lives in Söğüt.
It's true. They are very satisfied.
I heard that they don't pay
high taxes as we do.
They do not interfere with
their religion too.
We couldn't satisfy the
Lords for years.
Inegol Castle.
Priest Gregor came to your village and
gave a speech that praises Osman Bey.
Your people were greatly
affected by this speech.
Argos.
It seems that Osman learned where
the caravan is.
That's why he sent the Priest for the
speech.
The Priest is still in the village.
I think we can get him.
We have nothing to do with
the Priest anymore.
There is something more important.
But Osman has it.
Otherwise, Osman wouldn't send the Priest
that easy and without protection.
Position your soldiers
well in the village, Argus.
Osman knows that the caravan
will come to the village.
But he doesn't know that we know this.
I will prepare a big surprise for him.
A very big surprise.
Harmankaya Castle.
I heard what you wanted me to learn while
the Priest was talking to someone else.
It is a piece of the cross.
It is said that the piece is from the
cross that Jesus Christ was crucified.
What?
The cross on which Jesus Christ
was crucified.
Do you realize what you are saying,
Bahadır?
Yes. They are saying it's true.
Are you sure that it is the
cross of Jesus Christ?
Yes, Lord Kosses. I'm sure.
Bahadır.
You can't even imagine the importance
of this information that you brought.
These golds are for the information.
Think what you can get...
If you can bring me the relic
you speak of.
I will do it, Lord Kosses.
You will do it.
And don't you dare to forget...
Bahadır.
Punishment and reward are twins.
Don't you dare to return empty-handed.
Look at this, Maria.
Look at Osman Bey.
He holds the heart of the Christian world
in his hands.
But that heart should be in the hands
of the one who deserves it, brother.
Yes.
If we can get the relic, Maria...
not also Bithynia but the whole of Rome
will be down on its knees.
Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
She returned with an intelligence that
would make us victorious.
A caravan departed from Damascus.
According to the information we got,
the belongings of Kosses, Nicolo...
and even Rogatus are in that caravan.
Ten times more than what we got before.
Silk, spices, and all kinds of jewelry.
It is full of heavy goods.
The destination of this caravan is
Kastelion.
A village near the castle we call Kestel.
My Bey, it is possible to get there
without stepping our land.
It is their land for now, Demirci.
But before the caravan comes, that village
will be under our control.
Inshallah.
My Bey.
This is a cause of war.
You are talking about getting land.
Lord and even the
Emperors will be after us.
We've been at war since
the day we got the Priest.
It's not the time to pray.
Everyone will act according to
their nature.
They will go into their holes like
snakes and we will fight like wolves.
Let the preparations be made
until tomorrow.
Now is the time of the conquest.
As you ordered, my Bey.
Yes, my Bey.
If you allow, I want to be a part of this
bright conquest, my Bey.
When there are so many soldiers waiting
to be martyred, is this the right time?
If you come, what will Orhan do?
He doesn't have only one mother, my
Bey. Orhan is our Orhan.
Bala is his mother too.
Until I come back, his other mother can
look after him, can't you, Bala Hatun?
Of course.
Of course, I will look after my Orhan.
Malhun Hatun has longed for war
for a long time, my Bey.
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
Thank you.
If so, get ready, Malhun.
Then it's time to sharpen the weapons,
my Bey.
I will go to Davut Usta.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
-Thank you, Gonca.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you, my Hatun.
Here you go, let's eat.
In the name of Allah.
Enjoy your meal.
Why are you not eating?
What's wrong with you?
You are Osman Bey's head Alp.
Göktuğ.
You can't be in a bad mood.
Even though I disappointed my Bey?
You are thinking only about yourself.
While our Bey is saying to be together,
you are being selfish. Don't.
Because Turgut Bey brought their
carcasses, you are languishing.
I'm not being selfish, Boran. Turgut
Bey is the one who is being selfish.
You saw how he bragged.
People see what they want to see.
Our Bey's ambition is to unite
all the Turks.
Instead of being happy that Turgut Bey
is fighting by our side...
you are languishing.
Brother, the enemy is one, we are one.
Don't do this.
You are telling the truth. But what
bothers me is...
Brother. What is important for Osman Bey
is important for us.
Don't do this, Göktuğ.
Come on. Let's eat now.
Thank you, brother.
-Good luck with it, Malhun Hatun.
-Thank you, Bala.
Let me help you.
Don't carry it.
Alaca.
Do you want to go to the war too?
Are you bored here too?
Be a little patient, Alaca.
After Bala Hatun gives birth, you can
go to any war you want.
Inshallah.
Malhun Hatun.
My Orhan.
My child.
My brave child.
You are cold.
Let me take him. I will keep him
warm, do not worry.
His mother Bala will look after my Orhan.
I will not worry at all.
I know that you will look after him
as he is your own child.
Of course.
While you are fighting with the enemy,
we will pray here.
More power to your elbow, Malhun
Hatun.
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
-Cerkutay!
-My bey.
Go now.
But keep your eyes open.
Let's see the situation in the village.
Let's see what's awaiting us.
If you allow me, my bey.
Aren't we friends, Malhun Hatun?
What did I do to deserve this?
Stay calm, Gökçe girl.
Why are you talking to yourself?
I'm busy, Bahadır Bey.
Annoy someone else.
Gökçe girl.
You are from Kızılbeyoğlu Tribe.
I know your childhood.
You were nimble.
It doesn't you to bow your head like this.
Raise your head.
Here.
Take it.
Don't lower your head that easily.
Let it remind you who you are.
Patrol there.
And you, there.
You, there.
You protect the gate.
Master Gregor.
Your influence on the people is great.
They were impressed by your
speech yesterday.
But that speech will benefit Osman.
Don't you think that you help him
too much?
Andreas, let us be useful for Osman.
For now, what we need is to gain Osman's
trust. I told you.
You go this way!
Master, the street is full of
Lord Nikola's soldiers.
There wasn't this many yesterday.
Maybe this is Osman's plan.
What is Osman up to again?
I can catch up to his intelligence.
Mashallah!
Malhun! You look full of life because
of the battle.
I am! We haven't fought side by
side for too long.
True!
Cerkutay!
The village is like a hell. There are
soldiers everywhere.
What is it, Cerkutay?
Are you afraid?
I'm Osman Bey's alp. Does fear suit
us when we are with you, my bey?
True!
Alps!
They want to scotch the Kayı
and punish us!
Those who spill blood on the bread
of my people...
will be punished by me!
If they scotch our trade, we scotch
their caravans!
-Boran!
-My bey.
Bring the reports.
As you order, my bey.
İnegöl Border Village
Near Kastelion
Listen to me well now.
It's market time in the village.
It's full of people.
So, you will hide well.
There will be an alp for every
one of them.
Cerkutay.
You will reach the narrow street.
You know how to hide well.
Malhun, Aygül; you will disguise
us villager women.
I will be there too.
With my alps.
We'll strike down the patrolling
soldiers first.
With many tricks and traps,
no one will leave any mark behind.
They will be hanged.
The most important thing is, you will
look out for each other.
Soldiers!
My God, protect us.
The arrow came this way!
Run! Run!
Where are they?
Allah is eternal!
Come on, Andreas.
Alps!
Gather the people in the center.
As you order my bey!
Now I understand why you sent
me here, Osman Bey.
It's good that you do, Priest Gregor.
This is the only thing I want to see.
For the Christian people to catch
their breath under the flag of Kayı.
Come on.
What is it, Argus?
Are you afraid of Osman?
Sir.
-You said they might be in the village.
-And?
We put many soldiers in the village.
Isn't that so?
Yes, sir.
Then, there is no need for fear.
I don't like cowards.
If Osman is expecting us in the village.
Let us wait a little longer to
make him more impatient.
More.
I am Ertuğrul Ghazi's son, Osman Bey!
The bey of the Kayı!
I'm known by some of you.
The rest will start from now.
We don't plunder the lands
we conquer.
We revive them.
We make them home.
And we know that those who rule with
tyranny will go to hell.
For this reason, we are only afraid
of Allah!
Our laws are his laws.
And from now...
your property, your lives...
and your faith is protected by me!
Your taxes are in half.
Stay in ease.
People!
I've lived with Osman Bey for a while.
As I told him that he can't keep me a
captive, he would say that I'm a guest.
In the meantime, I saw that there is
no captivity under Osman Bey's banner.
There is only freedom, justice,
and mercy.
If you have something to say,
say it now.
And those who feel content go
to their home now.
May God protect you, Osman Bey.
We stand with whoever Priest Gregor
stands with.
Thank you. What good did the lord
do for us anyway?
My bey, the caravan
is near.
Let them come.
Long live Osman Bey!
Mashallah!
The valiants of the Kayı...
are idolizing Osman Bey!
Do you know who Osman Bey
idolizes?
Who is it?
Shah-ı Mardan.
The shah of the braves.
He idolizes Hz.Ali.
Hz.Ali's courage knows no limits!
He jumps on his white horse
and comes.
He takes us to Mecca.
-Should he take you to Mecca?
-Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Our dear prophet's army sieged
Hayber.
The siege lasted 20 whole days.
The number of martyrs
increased every day.
There were more than 2000 martyrs
and more than 5000 wounded.
But there is no yielding!
Does it suit a Muslim to give up?
It doesn't!
Great commanders stood on the gates
of Hayber Castle.
But no one can open it!
Our dear prophet took his black banner
on his holy hand.
He told Selman-ı Talisi to
call Ali.
Selman was surprised.
Hz.Ali was next to our holy prophet
with his sick eyes.
Our dear prophet prays for Ali's
sick eyes to heal.
He gives him the black flag.
And say that the conquest of Hayber
will happen with you.
Can he stop?
It's the holy prophet's words.
Hz.Ali didn't even wait for the soldiers!
He took the banner and Zülfikar.
And he ran to the hell-like battlefield!
Allah Allah!
Alarm in Hayber and curiosity
among the Jews!
Who is this man running at our
army on his own?
So, who are you, they said.
Our minister Ali replied...
I am Shah-ı Mardan.
Soldier of the battlefield,
the Lion of Allah...
Abu Talib's son, Ali!
The Jews shouted in confusion!
So, you are the one they
call Ali?
I am the one they call Ali.
The sword I'm wielding is called Zülfikar!
It doesn't let the heathens rest.
The arm that's wielding it has never been
beaten by anyone before!
The heathens said,
why should we be afraid of you?
You are a human just like us.
Made of bones and flesh.
Shah-ı Mardan Ali said...
yes, true.
I'm a human, made of bones and flesh,
just like you.
But I have such a power that...
gives me the confidence I need.
Allah Allah!
Hz.Ali takes the banner in his hand!
He rides his horse to the ditch!
He passes that great ditch as if
he is a bird!
He gets to the Hayber gates that
no one can pass!
He holds the gate latches tightly...
with his strong arms...
and pull them so hard that...
he pulls them so had that...
finally, the gate is broken!
There, the gate of Hayber gets
open for the Muslims.
Where does Hz.Ali's power comes from?
It's his faith, Ahmed.
It's his faith.
To make the heathens kneel...
before the power on your arms...
you need the power
of faith.
to be an alp!
A lion's heart, a steel arm and faith,
and the prophet's principles are needed.
Like Osman Bey, right?
Like Osman Bey, yes.
Osman Bey is like a Zülfikar
pointing the sun.
The oppressed take shelter
under its shadow.
The heathens are shattering away!
Mashallah!
Nikola!
Welcome to Kayı lands!
We were expecting you.
Oh, Osman Bey.
I never thought you would be here!
This is our land and the caravan
is our caravan now.
Is that what you say?
Do you think you can take this village by
killing my soldiers?
This is my village and this
is my caravan.
Don't be so sure!
We came as you wanted, Nikola.
Let's not keep Osman waiting.
As you see, Osman Bey.
It's still my village and it's
still my caravan.
I know you well enough to not
fall into your traps.
Nikola!
Do you know me too?
Do you know Turgut Bey too?
Even if you don't, you will now.
The caravan is important. Its sound
will echo in the whole of Bhytinia.
I sent the priest. Nikola must've
taken his precautions.
The weasels move in packs.
We shouldn't be alone.
Stand with us.
It's time to have some time
with Nikola.
I'll be there with my alps.
The wolf survived the winter...
but he won't forget the
cold he endured.
It's time for revenge, Osman Bey.
Charge!
Ya Allah!
Anselmo fights for gold but doesn't
die for gold.
Catalonians! We are retreating!
-We need to leave!
-Osman!
-We must leave, sir!
-Wait!
Stop!
How are we any different than
Judas who betrayed Jesus?
We left Christian lands to the Turks.
What did Osman Bey do?
He ruled his lands with justice!
He beat the tyrants!
What did Osman Bey do?
He spread the cause of the
Turks!
What did Osman Bey do!
Osman Bey conquered these lands!
What did Osman Bey do?
Osman Bey conquered hearts!
Osman Bey built the foundations
of the new Turkic state!
Osman Bey searched for a sky
for his holy banner...
he looked for a place to wave it!
He searched for land to place
his flag!
He found it. Now, even if the whole world
unites, it makes no difference!
Long live Osman Bey!
I'm Ertuğrul Ghazi's son,
Bey of the Kayı, Osman Bey!
Now, this village belongs to the Turks!
With strong horses...
brave alps...
we ran after a dream!
Now, thanks to Allah we reached
another point!
Thank Allah!
We expanded our home, thank Allah!
But this cause is greater
than one lifetime.
There are many other castles to conquer
and many other cities to control!
And there are many oppressed under
the rule of the tyrants!
But my sword of justice is closer to their
necks than ever!
Now, they all wait for their turn!
An order for the world,
peace for the hearts...
and pain for the heathens
is coming!
Allahu Akbar!
''Surely, we destined you a
decisive conquest.''
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com